

CONTACT

- +020 93 087 243
- Vientiane Center Lao, Laos
- www.crazybestdev.com

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022 National University of Laos

Software Engineer(AHT)

2015 - 2018 Vientiane High School

SKILLS

- Software Development
- Web Development
- Web3 Development
- Problem Solving
- Team Collaboration
- Code Review
- Version Control (Git)
- Communication Skill

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Chinese (Intermediate)

XIAO FEI

Senior FullStack Web Developer

Summary

Senior FullStack Web Developer

I am a senior fullstack web developer with 6 years of experience in developing web, mobile and web3 applications. I specialize in creating software solutions across diverse range of industries including **Ecommerce**, healthcare, real estate and social media.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Newwave Solutions

Jan 2022 - Sep 2023

FullStack Developer

- Built animation-focused websites using React JS, GSAP, and the Locomotive Scroll library, seamlessly integrated with Concrete CMS, resulting in 100% easy content management.
- I made the web pages load more than 50% faster. Performance and speed were key points of the

TPS Software

May 2018 - Jan 2022

UI & Frontend Developer

- Re-designed over 85 unique pages for B2B, CRM, and corporate websites in Figma.
- Collaborated closely with two backend developers and created the frontend of the entire project.
- Made sure the pages loaded super fast, scoring over 90 in page speed.

Enlab Software Company

Apr 2017 - May 2018

Marketing Manager & Specialist

- Developed and maintained functional pages for web applications.
- Worked with a .NET based custom CMS.

CORE SKILLSET

Frontend

JS, TS, React, Vue, Next, Gatsby, Svelte, MUI, chakraUI, Tailwind CSS

Backend

Node.js, Express, PHP, Laravel, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL HeadlessCMS